¬text for event images
{SMT_A_NEW_MAN__GAIUS_MARIUS_TITLE}	A New Man: Gaius Marius
{SMT_A_NEW_MAN__GAIUS_MARIUS_BODY}	Gaius Marius has proposed a series of laws that allow the proletariat to join his reorganised Roman army. In return for many years of military service every soldier will be given land as a kind of pension. This reform is passed in the people's assembly without the approval of the Senate. It's a certainty that such popular - and populist - appeal will do Marius no favours in the long run!\n\nThe troop types available for recruitment now reflect the structure of this new professional army. Check the recruitment scroll to view the details.
{roman_empire_unstable_currency}	Currency Crisis!
{roman_empire_unstable_currency_body}	The policies of debasement and inflation pursued by previous emperors have undermined all trust in our currency, and it is no longer favoured as a medium of exchange. Some have even reverted to bartering, so low is trust in Roman coin!\n\nUntil we can restore faith in our coin, you will be unable to recruit Merchants to trade in foreign lands.
{roman_empire_stable_currency}	Currency Crisis Resolved
{roman_empire_stable_currency_body}	Our recent investments in mining has worked wonders; we now have the resources to produce coins of high intrinsic worth, and faith in Roman coin is restoring across the world!\n\nYou can now recruit Merchants in settlements with a Market or better.
{miaphysite_heresy}	A New Heresy Arises!
{miaphysite_heresy_body}	 A dangerous heresy has erupted in your lands, spreading false beliefs and corrupting the minds of the innocent. This heresy poses a threat to the stability of your society and the unity of your empire. Be at arms, for the heretics will plan to strike..